让我们总结一下我们学到的东西。
Let’s summarise what we’ve learned.
相机对于机器人而言是一个非常精彩的传感器，但它会产生无法使用的效果
The camera is a really wonderful sensor for a robot to have, but it produces an unusable
数据洪流。
torrent of data.
像素太多了。
There are just too many pixels.
比机器人更多的像素可以动作。
Far more pixels than a robot can action.
所以我们需要做的是简化这个数据流并找到有意义的对象
So what we need to do is to simplify this stream of data and to find meaningful objects
在机器人可以响应，移动到的任何数据流中。
within that stream of data that a robot can respond to, move to, whatever.
因此，区域是具有相似强度或颜色的一组相邻像素。
So a region is a set of adjacent pixels with a similar intensity or colour.
我们已经讨论了在场景中查找区域的技术。
We’ve talked about techniques to find regions within a scene.
我们使用一种称为区域标记的技术来区分多个不同的对象
We’ve use a technique called region labelling to distinguish multiple distinct objects that
存在于单个二进制图像中。
exist within a single binary image.
一旦我们标记了区域，我们就可以提取特征来描述每个区域
Once we have labelled regions, then we can extract features to describe each of those
区域。
regions.
我们在场景中有多个区域，对于每个区域我们都可以确定
We have multiple regions within the scene, and for each of them we can determine the
区域的位置，区域的大小，区域的形状和方向。
position of the region, the size of the region, the shape of the region, and its orientation.
我们已经讨论了测量和估计所有这些事情的技术，并进行了演示
We’ve talked about techniques to measure and estimate all of these things, and demonstrated
如何使用MATLAB和MATLAB工具箱完成很多这些工作。
how to do a lot of these things using MATLAB and the MATLAB tool box.